<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on Kevlyn Kadamala</title>
    <link>https://kad99kev.github.io/categories/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on Kevlyn Kadamala</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kad99kev.github.io/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Life/Luck Abroad</title>
      <link>https://kad99kev.github.io/klog/life-abroad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kad99kev.github.io/klog/life-abroad/</guid>
      <description>On the 6th of September 2022, I completed a year in Ireland. A year that feels almost a moment ago. Many memories made, and most certainly happy ones. I consider myself very lucky to be where I am. While I believe in hard work, I never underestimate the role that luck has played in my journey so far.
The National University of Ireland, Galway (now University of Galway) was my first choice of university.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Experience as the Captain of the Football Team</title>
      <link>https://kad99kev.github.io/klog/experience-as-captain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kad99kev.github.io/klog/experience-as-captain/</guid>
      <description>If I had to sum up my experience as the captain of my college football team into a single word, it&amp;rsquo;d be - Grateful
It wasn&amp;rsquo;t an easy start for me. Most of it was because of the confidence (or lack thereof) in myself. I doubted my ability as a football player and as a leader. I was afraid of being a failure. It was a big responsibility and the last thing I would want to do is lose the respect of my players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting into Habits</title>
      <link>https://kad99kev.github.io/klog/getting-into-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kad99kev.github.io/klog/getting-into-habits/</guid>
      <description>I started with the habit of reading. It was more of a new year&amp;rsquo;s resolution. It was difficult at first, trying to read everyday. My plan initially was to read atleast one chapter a day. I knew I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be able to maintain this habit, but I was really really determined to complete atleast one book a month. It&amp;rsquo;s May now, and I think my determination paid off. I&amp;rsquo;ve so far read The Little Prince by Antoine de Saint-Exupéry in January, Animal Farm by George Orwell in February, Rich Dad Poor Dad by Robert Kiyosaki in March and Storm in a Teacup by Helen Czerski in April.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
